Guide to the Harvey Williams Cushing Papers in the Yale University Library
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Papers held in Manuscripts and Archives, Part I
  - Correspondence, 1884-1939; Series I; 29 linear feet (70 boxes, 55 reels)
    - Howland, Joseph B., 1933-1938 (Box 36, Folder 717, Reel 30)
      See also: Series II, Folders 173-177, 309, 775, 797-809
    - Hubbard, Joshua C.
      See: Series II, Folders 433-436
    - Huber, G. C.
      See: Series II, Folder 786
    - Hume, Edgar Erskine, 1933-1939 (Box 36, Folder 718, Reel 30)
    - Hume, Edward H., 1919-1932 (Box 36, Folder 719, Reel 30)
    - Humpton, B. O.
      See: Series II, Folder 544
    - Hundley, Joseph H.
      See: Series II, Folders 21, 27
    - Hunnewell, Francis W. Jr., 1914-1925 (Box 36, Folder 720, Reel 30)
    - Huntington, George S. Huntington, Mrs. George S., 1922-1930 (Box 36, Folder 721, Reel 30)
      See also: Series II, Folder 907
    - Hurd, Henry M., 1914-1931 (Box 36, Folder 722, Reel 30)
      See also: Series II, Folder 545
    - Hurry, Jamieson B.
      See: Series II, Folder 542
    - Husted, Mary S.
      See: Series II, Folder 753
    - Huth, Ch.
      See: Series II, Folder 79
    - Hyde, James E., 1921 (Box 36, Folder 723, Reel 30)
    - Ic-Ins (Box 37, Folder 724, Reel 30)
    - Int-Io (Box 37, Folder 725, Reel 30)
    - Ir-Iv (Box 37, Folder 726, Reel 30)
    - Index Medicus, 1922-1924 (Box 37, Folder 727, Reel 30)
    - Ingersoll, J. W. D., 1911-1926, undated (Box 37, Folder 728, Reel 30)
      See also: Series III, Folder 310
    - Ingram, Myrtle
      See: Folder 336
    - Ingram, W. H., Jr.
    - International Grenfell Association, 1919-1931 (Box 37, Folder 729, Reel 30)
    - Ireland, Merritte W., 1919-1931 (Box 37, Folder 730, Reel 30)
      See also: Folder 1038; Series II, Folder 15
    - Ireland, Pansy
      See: Series II, Folder 932
    - Irsay, Stephen d', 1925, 1931 (Box 37, Folder 731, Reel 30)
    - Israel, Max
      See: Series II, Folder 721
    - Jac (Box 37, Folder 732, Reel 30)
    - Jae-Jay (Box 37, Folder 733, Reel 30)
    - Jea-Johns Hopkins (Box 37, Folder 734, Reel 30)
    - Johnson-Jon (Box 37, Folder 735, Reel 31)
    - Jop-Ju (Box 37, Folder 736, Reel 31)
    - Jackson, Byron H.
      See: Series II, Folder 674
    - Jackson, Chevalier, 1917-1933 (Box 37, Folder 737, Reel 31)
      See also: Series II, Folders 36, 391
    - Jackson, Henry, 1920-1933 (Box 37, Folder 738, Reel 31)
    - Jackson, Herbert
    - Jackson, Holmes C., 1921-1924 (Box 37, Folder 739, Reel 31)
    - Jackson, James, 1922-1923 (Box 37, Folder 740, Reel 31)
    - Jacobaeus, H. C., 1922-1931 (Box 37, Folder 741, Reel 31)
    - Jacobs, Henry Barton, 1903-1911, 1915-1930 (Box 37, Folder 742, Reel 31)
      See also: Series II, Folders 549, 709, 906-907
    - Jacobs, Henry Barton, 1931-1939 (Box 37, Folder 743, Reel 31)
      See also: Series II, Folders 906-907
    - Jacobson, Conrad, 1919-1931 (Box 37, Folder 744, Reel 31)
    - Jacobson, Victor C., 1920-1929 (Box 38, Folder 745, Reel 31)
    - Jakob, Alfons, 1924-1934 (Box 38, Folder 746, Reel 31)
    - James, Henry
      See: Series II, Folder 547
    - James, Walter B., 1908, 1914-1916 (Box 38, Folder 747, Reel 31)
    - Japan Medical Congress
      See: Series II, Folder 488
    - Jeanneney, G., 1924-1927 (Box 38, Folder 748, Reel 31)
    - Jefferson, Geoffery, 1919-1939 (Box 38, Folder 749, Reel 31)
      See also: Series II, Folder 547
    - Jelliffe, Smith Ely
      See: Series II, Folders 386, 654, 658
    - Jenkins, Mrs. L. D.
    - John, Arthur Jukes
      See: Series II, Folder 550
    - Johns Hopkins Hospital, 1898, 1914- 1922 (Box 38, Folder 750, Reel 31)
      See also: Series II, Folders 490-491
    - Johns Hopkins University, 1902-1934 (Box 38, Folder 751, Reel 31)
      See also: Series II, Folder 492
    - Johnson, F. B.
      See: Series II, Folder 236
    - Johnson, James Bovell
      See: Series II, Folder 551
    - Johnson, L. H. H.
      See: Series II, Folders 9, 309, 762-763, 778, 782, 784-785, 789-791, 809
    - Jones, Harold W.
      See: Series II, Folders 876, 893
    - Jones, Sir Robert, 1925-1927 (Box 38, Folder 752, Reel 31)
      See also: Series II, Folder 813
    - Jordan Marsh Company, 1921-1937 (Box 38, Folder 753, Reel 31)
    - Josephson, Adolph
    - Joslin, Elliott P., 1915-1939 (Box 38, Folder 754, Reel 31)
      See also: Series II, Folders 380, 401-402
    - Jossmann, Paul
    - Judd, J. R., 1936-1939 (Box 38, Folder 755, Reel 31)
    - Ka (Box 38, Folder 756, Reel 31)
    - Kea-Kem (Box 38, Folder 757, Reel 31)
    - Ken-Key (Box 38, Folder 758, Reel 31)
    - Kh-Ki (Box 38, Folder 759, Reel 31)
    - Kl-Kok (Box 38, Folder 760, Reel 31)
    - Kon-Ky (Box 38, Folder 761, Reel 31)
    - Kaplan, Abraham, 1928-1938 (Box 38, Folder 762, Reel 31)
    - Karsner, Howard T., 1919-1935, undated (Box 38, Folder 763, Reel 31)
    - Kast, Ludwig, 1935 (Box 38, Folder 764, Reel 31)
      See also: Series II, Folders 942-943
    - Kayes, Chester B.
      See: Series II, Folder 22
    - Kean, J. R.
      See: Series II, Folders 15-16
    - Kebabjian, Hrant S., 1921-1923, undated (Box 38, Folder 765, Reel 32)
    - Keegan, J. Jay, 1921-1934 (Box 38, Folder 766, Reel 32)
      See also: Series II, Folder 346
    - Keen, Florence, 1932-1938 (Box 38, Folder 767, Reel 32)
    - Keen, W. W., 1900-1913 (Box 38, Folder 768, Reel 32)
    - Keen, W. W., 1915-1929 (Box 39, Folder 769, Reel 32)
      See also: Folders 35, Series II, Folders 36, 188, 333-335, 554
    - Keith, Sir Arthur, 1919-1935 (Box 39, Folder 770, Reel 32)
      See also: Series II, Folder 552
    - Keller, Allen D., 1933-1936 (Box 39, Folder 771, Reel 32)
    - Keller, Deane, 1935-1939 (Box 39, Folder 772, Reel 32)
    - Kelley, A. J.
    - Kellogg, Frederick S., 1909, 1927-1928 (Box 39, Folder 773, Reel 32)
    - Kelly, Howard A., 1898-1939 (Box 39, Folder 774, Reel 32)
      See also: Series II, Folders 232, 552
    - Kennedy, Foster, 1916-1938 (Box 39, Folder 775, Reel 32)
    - Kenney, V. W., 1925-1932 (Box 39, Folder 776, Reel 32)
    - Keogh, Andrew, 1920-1937 (Box 39, Folder 779, Reel 32)
      See also: Folders 1575-1576; Series II, Folders 926-928, 932
    - Kernohan, James W.
      See: Series II, Folder 668
    - Kerr, Harry Hyland, 1919-1936 (Box 39, Folder 777, Reel 32)
    - Kerr, William J., 1915-1932 (Box 39, Folder 778, Reel 32)
    - Kessel, Franz K., 1935-1939 (Box 39, Folder 780, Reel 32)
      See also: Series II, Folders 474, 476
    - Key, Einar, 1921-1938 (Box 39, Folder 781, Reel 32)
    - Keynes, Geoffery Keynes, Margaret, 1922-1939 (Box 39, Folder 782, Reel 32)
    - Kibre, Adèle, 1938-1939 (Box 39, Folder 783, Reel 32)
    - Kibre, Pearl, 1938-1939 (Box 39, Folder 784, Reel 32)
    - King, Frank L.
      See: Series II, Folders 173-177
    - King, John
      See: Folder 310
    - King, Raphael
      See: Series II, Folders 82-83
    - Kingsbury, John A.
      See: Series II, Folder 917
    - Kingsley Trust Association, 1914-1938 (Box 39, Folder 785, Reel 32)
    - Kittredge, George Lyman, 1931-1936 (Box 39, Folder 786, Reel 32)
    - Klebs, Arnold C., 1929-1930 (Box 39, Folder 787, Reel 32)
      See also: Series II, Folders 296, 555; MHL
    - Kleijn, A. de
    - Kmotrick, Frank, 1923-1936 (Box 39, Folder 788, Reel 32)
    - Kmotrick, Josephine, 1914-1932 (Box 39, Folder 789, Reel 32)
    - Knapp, Arnold, 1916-1932 (Box 39, Folder 790, Reel 32)
      See also: Series II, Folders 635, 642, 645
    - Kneeland, Edward
    - Knollenberg, Bernhard
      See: Series II, Folder 930
    - Knopf, S. Adolphus, 1916, 1935 (Box 39, Folder 791, Reel 32)
      See also: Series II, Folder 553
    - Kocher, Albert, 1907, 1922- 1931 (Box 39, Folder 792, Reel 32)
    - Kocher, Theodor, 1901-1922 (Box 40, Folder 793, Reel 32)
    - Kolodny, Anatole, 1922-1923 (Box 40, Folder 794, Reel 33)
    - Kramer, Raymond C.
    - Kraus, E. J.
    - Kraus, Hans P.
      See: Series II, Folder 84
    - Kraus, Walter M., 1923-1938 (Box 40, Folder 795, Reel 33)
    - Krause, Allen K., 1922-1929 (Box 40, Folder 796, Reel 33)
    - Kredel, Frederick E., 1928-1937 (Box 40, Folder 797, Reel 33)
      See also: Series II, Folder 818
    - Kroenecker, Charlotte, 1921-1936 (Box 40, Folder 798, Reel 33)
    - Krumbhaar, Edward B., 1920-1929 (Box 40, Folder 799, Reel 33)
    - Kubie, Lawrence S., 1926-1936 (Box 40, Folder 800, Reel 33)
    - La-Lam (Box 40, Folder 801, Reel 33)
    - Lan-Law (Box 40, Folder 802, Reel 33)
    - Le (Box 40, Folder 803, Reel 33)
    - Lh-Ll (Box 40, Folder 804, Reel 33)
    - Lo (Box 40, Folder 805, Reel 33)
    - Lu (Box 40, Folder 806, Reel 33)
    - Lw-Ly (Box 40, Folder 807, Reel 33)
    - Ladd, William E., 1930-1937 (Box 40, Folder 808, Reel 33)
    - Lafleur, H. A.
      See: Series II, Folder 556
    - Lahey, Frank H., 1921-1939 (Box 40, Folder 809, Reel 33)
      See also: Series II, Folder 361
    - Laing, James H. W.
      See: Series II, Folder 636
    - Lambert, Samuel W., 1919-1939 (Box 40, Folder 810, Reel 33)
      See also: Series II, Folders 904-905
    - Lancet
      See: Series II, Folders 556, 647
    - Lane, Alfred C.
      See: Folders 29-30
    - Lane, S. H.
      See: Series II, Folder 722
    - Lane, William C., 1917-1927 (Box 40, Folder 811, Reel 33)
    - Langworthy, Orthello R., 1928-1934 (Box 41, Folder 812, Reel 33)
    - Lanman, Thomas H., 1927-1933 (Box 41, Folder 813, Reel 33)
    - Larimore, F. C., 1928-1929 (Box 41, Folder 814, Reel 33)
    - Larkey, Sanford V., 1932-1939 (Box 41, Folder 815, Reel 33)
    - Larsen, Y. H.
      See: Series II, Folder 699
    - Lauwers, Emile E., 1924-1937 (Box 41, Folder 816, Reel 33)
    - Lawler, E. M.
    - Lawrence, John H., 1932-1939 (Box 41, Folder 817, Reel 33)
    - Lea and Febiger, Publishers
      See: Series II, Folder 558
    - Leake, Chauncey D., 1926-1938 (Box 41, Folder 818, Reel 33)
    - Learmonth, James R., 1927-1939 (Box 41, Folder 819, Reel 33)
    - Leary, Timothy, 1924-1936 (Box 41, Folder 820, Reel 33)
    - LeConte, Robert G., 1914-1922 (Box 41, Folder 821, Reel 33)
    - LeCount, Edwin R., 1919-1933 (Box 41, Folder 822, Reel 33)
    - Lee, Burton James, 1919-1920 (Box 41, Folder 823, Reel 33)
    - Lee, Ferdinand C., 1923-1932 (Box 41, Folder 824, Reel 33)
      See also: Series II, Folder 442
    - Lee, Frederick S., 1915-1926 (Box 41, Folder 825, Reel 33)
    - Lee, George C., 1917-1928 (Box 41, Folder 826, Reel 34)
    - Lee, Roger I., 1920-1937 (Box 41, Folder 827, Reel 34)
    - Lee, Walter Estell, 1925-1937 (Box 41, Folder 828, Reel 34)
    - Lee, Higginson and Co., 1915-1920 (Box 41, Folder 829, Reel 34)
    - Lee, Higginson and Co., 1921-1922 (Box 41, Folder 830, Reel 34)
    - Lee, Higginson and Co., 1923-1925 (Box 41, Folder 831, Reel 34)
    - Lee, Higginson and Co. Lee, Higginson Trust Co., 1926-1928 (Box 41, Folder 832, Reel 34)
    - Lee, Higginson Trust Co., 1929 (Box 41, Folder 833, Reel 34)
    - Lee, Higginson Trust Co., 1930-1931 (Box 41, Folder 834, Reel 34)
    - Lee, Higginson Trust Co. Lee, Higginson Corporation, 1932 (Box 41, Folder 835, Reel 34)
    - Leeb, Harry, 1937-1938 (Box 41, Folder 836, Reel 34)
    - LeFrançois, E.
      See: Series II, Folder 87
    - LeHand, Marguerite A., 1933-1939 (Box 41, Folder 837, Reel 34)
    - Lehman, Edwin P., 1916-1935 (Box 41, Folder 838, Reel 34)
    - Lehmann, Walter, 1926-1939 (Box 41, Folder 839, Reel 34)
      See also: Series II, Folder 823
    - Leidy, Joseph
      See: Series II, Folder 559
    - Leikind, Morris C., 1935-1939 (Box 41, Folder 840, Reel 34)
    - Leland, K. G.
      See: Series II, Folders 193-195
    - Lennander, K. G., 1906-1907 (Box 41, Folder 841, Reel 34)
    - Leonard, V. N., 1916 (Box 41, Folder 842, Reel 34)
    - Leriche, René, 1919-1939 (Box 41, Folder 843, Reel 34)
    - Leschke, Erich, 1932-1933 (Box 41, Folder 844, Reel 34)
    - Levi, Ettore, 1930-1931 (Box 42, Folder 845, Reel 34)
    - Levine, Laurence, 1931-1938 (Box 42, Folder 846, Reel 34)
    - Levine, Samuel A., 1923-1938 (Box 42, Folder 847, Reel 34)
    - Lewin, Philip, 1924-1934 (Box 42, Folder 848, Reel 34)
    - Lewis, Dean, 1915-1935 (Box 42, Folder 849, Reel 34)
      See also: Series II, Folders 643, 810
    - Lewis, Frederick T., 1917-1939 (Box 42, Folder 850, Reel 34)
      See also: Series II, Folders 393-397, 401, 402
    - Lewis (H. K.) and Co.
      See: Series II, Folder 88
    - Lewis, Sir Thomas, 1929-1937 (Box 42, Folder 851, Reel 34)
    - Lewis, Wilmarth S., 1930-1939 (Box 42, Folder 852, Reel 34)
    - Liber, Amour F., 1935-1936 (Box 42, Folder 853, Reel 34)
      See also: Series II, Folder 669
    - Libman, Emanuel, 1925-1935 (Box 42, Folder 854, Reel 34)
      See also: Series II, Folder 241
    - Library of Congress, 1925-1937 (Box 42, Folder 855, Reel 34)
    - Lie, Jonas, 1926-1931 (Box 42, Folder 856, Reel 34)
    - Liebel, George H., 1931-1936 (Box 42, Folder 857, Reel 34)
      See also: Series II, Folder 229
    - Lier, Reinhard
      See: Series II, Folder 893
    - Lier (R.) and Co.
      See: Series II, Folders 89-101
    - Life, 1939 (Box 42, Folder 858, Reel 34)
    - Light, Richard Upjohn, 1928-1939 (Box 42, Folder 859, Reel 34)
      See also: Series II, Folders 449-450, 767, 789, 791
    - Lilienthal, Howard, 1924 (Box 42, Folder 860, Reel 34)
    - Lillie, W. I., 1922-1925 (Box 42, Folder 861, Reel 34)
    - Lincoln, Albert O.
      See: Series II, Folder 297
    - Lindau, Arvid, 1928-1931 (Box 42, Folder 862, Reel 34)
      See also: Series II, Folders 878-879
    - Lindau, Arvid, 1932-1939 (Box 42, Folder 863, Reel 34)
    - Lindskog, Gustaf E.
      See: Series II, Folder 347
    - Lippincott (J. B.) Co., 1911, 1915-1934 (Box 42, Folder 864, Reel 34)
      See also: Series II, Folder 638
    - Lisser, Hans, 1921-1934 (Box 42, Folder 865, Reel 34)
    - List, Carl Felix, 1932-1937 (Box 42, Folder 866, Reel 34)
    - Little, Walter H., 1929 (Box 42, Folder 867, Reel 34)
    - Little, Brown and Co., 1928-1939 (Box 42, Folder 868, Reel 34)
    - Lium, Rolf, 1932-1937 (Box 42, Folder 869, Reel 35)
    - Livingston, William K., 1922-1934 (Box 42, Folder 870, Reel 35)
    - Lloyd (Andrew J.) Co., 1919-1926 (Box 42, Folder 871, Reel 35)
    - Lobingier, Andrew Stewart, 1915-1936 (Box 42, Folder 872, Reel 35)
    - Locke, Charles Edward, Jr., 1921-1929 (Box 42, Folder 873, Reel 35)
    - Locke, Charles F. A.
      See: Series II, Folder 557
    - Lockwood, A. L., 1922-1929 (Box 42, Folder 874, Reel 35)
    - Lohmann, Carl A., 1934 (Box 42, Folder 875, Reel 35)
      See also: Series II, Folders 923-924
    - Long, C. N. H., 1936-1937 (Box 42, Folder 876, Reel 35)
    - Long, Esmond R., 1930-1933 (Box 42, Folder 877, Reel 35)
    - Longcope, Warfield T., 1914-1933, undated (Box 42, Folder 878, Reel 35)
    - Looney, Joseph M., 1930 (Box 42, Folder 879, Reel 35)
    - Loring, Louisa P.
    - Lorthioir, Jules, 1914-1931 (Box 42, Folder 880, Reel 35)
    - Lovett, Elizabeth, 1924-1928, undated (Box 43, Folder 881, Reel 35)
    - Lovett, Robert W., 1915-1925 (Box 43, Folder 882, Reel 35)
      See also: Folder 881, Series II Folders 363, 427-428, 430, 433
    - Lovett (Robert) Memorial Foundation
      See: Folder 1069
    - Lowell, A. Lawrence, 1920-1927 (Box 43, Folder 883, Reel 35)
      See also: Series II, Folders 425, 434-435
    - Lowell, Amy, 1924-1925 (Box 43, Folder 884, Reel 35)
    - Lowes, John L., 1928-1932 (Box 43, Folder 885, Reel 35)
    - Ludwig, Frederick G.
    - Luger, Alfred P., 1912-1938 (Box 43, Folder 886, Reel 35)
    - Lund, Charles C., 1929-1935 (Box 43, Folder 887, Reel 35)
    - Lund, Fred B., 1914-1936 (Box 43, Folder 888, Reel 35)
    - Lusk, Graham, 1917-1931 (Box 43, Folder 889, Reel 35)
    - Lynch, Arthur L., 1933-1934 (Box 43, Folder 890, Reel 35)
    - Lyon, E. P., 1924-1925 (Box 43, Folder 891, Reel 35)
    - Maca-Macc (Box 43, Folder 892, Reel 35)
    - Macd-Macg (Box 43, Folder 893, Reel 35)
    - Mach-Macy (Box 43, Folder 894, Reel 35)
    - Mad-Mak (Box 43, Folder 895, Reel 35)
    - Mal-Map (Box 43, Folder 896, Reel 35)
    - Mar (Box 43, Folder 897, Reel 35)
    - Mas (Box 43, Folder 898, Reel 35)
    - Mat-May (Box 43, Folder 899, Reel 35)
    - Mea-Mei (Box 43, Folder 900, Reel 35)
    - Mel-Mey (Box 43, Folder 901, Reel 35)
    - Mic-Miller, R. (Box 43, Folder 902, Reel 35)
    - Miller, S.-Miy (Box 43, Folder 903, Reel 36)
    - Moc-Mon (Box 44, Folder 904, Reel 36)
    - Moo-Mor (Box 44, Folder 905, Reel 36)
    - Mos-Moy (Box 44, Folder 906, Reel 36)
    - Mu-My (Box 44, Folder 907, Reel 36)
    - MacAlister, Alexander
      See: Series II, Folder 560
    - MacAlister, Sir John Y. W., 1921-1924 (Box 44, Folder 908, Reel 36)
      See also: Series II, Folder 564
    - Macallum, A. B., 1906-1933 (Box 44, Folder 909, Reel 36)
      See also: Series II, Folder 565
    - McBean, George Martin, 1911, 1929 (Box 44, Folder 910, Reel 36)
    - MacCallum, George A.
      See: Series II, Folder 566
    - MacCallum, William G., 1900-1929 (Box 44, Folder 911, Reel 36)
      See also: Series II, Folders 386, 389, 560
    - MacCallum, William G., 1930-1939, undated (Box 44, Folder 912, Reel 36)
      See also: Series II, Folders 397, 460, 560
    - McCann, William S., 1917-1932 (Box 44, Folder 913, Reel 36)
    - McCarthy, Daniel J., 1914-1938 (Box 44, Folder 914, Reel 36)
      See also: Folder 310
    - MacCarty, William C., 1923-1934 (Box 44, Folder 915, Reel 36)
    - McClean, Arthur J.
      See: Series II, Folder 762
    - McClintock, Norman, 1920-1937 (Box 44, Folder 916, Reel 36)
    - McClintock, Walter, 1919-1930 (Box 44, Folder 917, Reel 36)
    - McClure, Roy D., 1916-1937 (Box 44, Folder 918, Reel 36)
    - McConnell, Francis J.
    - McCormick, Vance C., 1921-1923, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 919, Reel 36)
      See also: Series II, Folder 943
    - McCrae, Thomas, 1899-1903 (Box 44, Folder 920, Reel 36)
    - McCrae, Thomas, 1914-1932 (Box 44, Folder 921, Reel 36)
      See also: Series II, Folders 489, 567, 643
    - McDonald, William, Jr., 1921-1936 (Box 44, Folder 922, Reel 36)
    - McEachran, Duncan
    - McGill University. Montreal Neurological Institute, 1934 (Box 44, Folder 923, Reel 36)
      See also: Series II, Folder 560
    - McGregor, W. J.
      See: Series II, Folder 620
    - Macht, David I., 1929-1936 (Box 44, Folder 924, Reel 36)
    - McIntyre, James
      See: Series II, Folder 107
    - McIver, Monroe A., 1929-1934 (Box 44, Folder 925, Reel 36)
    - Mackall, Leonard L., 1916-1936 (Box 44, Folder 926, Reel 36)
      See also: Series II, Folder 568, 618
    - McKenzie, Albert, 1921-1935 (Box 44, Folder 927, Reel 36)
    - McKenzie, Kenneth, 1923-1939 (Box 45, Folder 928, Reel 37)
    - McKenzie, R. Tait, 1914-1938 (Box 45, Folder 929, Reel 37)
    - McLanahan, Duer
      See: Series II, Folders 701-702
    - McLean, Arthur J. McLean, G. B., 1929-1939 (Box 45, Folder 930, Reel 37)
      See also: Series II, Folder 767
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1923-1939 (Box 45, Folder 931, Reel 37)
    - Macleod, J. J. R., 1917-1933 (Box 45, Folder 932, Reel 37)
    - MacMahon, Edward, 1933-1935 (Box 45, Folder 933, Reel 37)
    - Macmillan Co., 1935-1939 (Box 45, Folder 934, Reel 37)
      See also: Series II, Folder 569
    - MacMurchy, Helen
      See: Series II, Folder 570
    - MacNalty, Arthur Salusbury, 1925-1939 (Box 45, Folder 935, Reel 37)
      See also: Series II, Folder 561
    - McNee, J. W., 1926-1936 (Box 45, Folder 936, Reel 37)
    - MacNider, William deB., 1925-1938 (Box 45, Folder 937, Reel 37)
    - Maddock, S. J.
      See: Series II, Folders 444, 447-448
    - Maes, Urban, 1928-1936 (Box 45, Folder 938, Reel 37)
    - Maggs Brothers
      See: Series II, Folders 108-111
    - Mahoney, William deG., 1932-1938 (Box 45, Folder 939, Reel 37)
    - Major, Ralph H., 1928-1939, undated (Box 45, Folder 940, Reel 37)
    - Makins, Sir George Makins, Lady M. A., 1915, 1924-1926 (Box 45, Folder 941, Reel 37)
    - Mall, Franklin P., 1899-1915 (Box 45, Folder 942, Reel 37)
    - Malloch, Archibald, 1905-1921 (Box 45, Folder 943, Reel 37)
      See also: Series II, Folders 571, 902
    - Malloch, Archibald, 1922-1923 (Box 45, Folder 944, Reel 37)
    - Malloch, Archibald, 1924-1930 (Box 45, Folder 945, Reel 37)
      See also: Series II, Folders 192, 571, 902
    - Malloch, Archibald, 1931-1934 (Box 45, Folder 946, Reel 37)
      See also: Series II, Folders 194-195, 571, 651, 902, 904-905
    - Malloch, Archibald, 1935-1939, undated (Box 45, Folder 947, Reel 37)
      See also: Series II, Folders 194-195, 651, 893, 902, 905
    - Mallory, Frank B., 1916-1937 (Box 45, Folder 948, Reel 37)
    - Malone, Dumas
    - Maltby (A.) and Son, 1930-1939 (Box 45, Folder 949, Reel 37)
    - Marburg, Otto, 1922-1939 (Box 45, Folder 950, Reel 37)
    - Marine, David, 1921-1937 (Box 45, Folder 951, Reel 37)
    - Martel, Thierry de, 1915-1939 (Box 46, Folder 952, Reel 37)
    - Martin, Charles F., 1908-1934 (Box 46, Folder 953, Reel 37)
    - Martin, Edward, 1907-1927 (Box 46, Folder 954, Reel 37)
      See also: Folder 1331
    - Martin, Edward S., 1933-1935 (Box 46, Folder 955, Reel 37)
    - Martin, Franklin H. Martin, Elizabeth, 1905, 1915- 1936 (Box 46, Folder 956, Reel 37)
      See also: Folders 35-41; Series II, Folders 36, 232, 641, 644, 648, 659
    - Martin, Marianne R., 1931-1932 (Box 46, Folder 957, Reel 37)
    - Martin, Paul, 1922-1939 (Box 46, Folder 958, Reel 37)
      See also: Series II, Folders 306, 448
    - Mason, Paul C.
      See: Series II, Folder 656
    - Massachusetts Historical Society, 1926-1935 (Box 46, Folder 959, Reel 37)
    - Massachusetts General Hospital, 1915-1939 (Box 46, Folder 960, Reel 37)
    - Massachusetts Medical Benevolent Society, 1930-1932 (Box 46, Folder 961, Reel 37)
    - Massachusetts Medical Society, 1915-1935, undated (Box 46, Folder 962, Reel 38)
    - Matas, Rudolph, 1908, 1920-1936 (Box 46, Folder 963, Reel 38)
      See also: Series II, Folders 812, 865
    - Mather, Samuel, 1913-1931 (Box 46, Folder 964, Reel 38)
    - Mathews (Elkin), Ltd.
      See: Series II, Folder 112
    - Matthews, Mrs. Alexander
      See: Series II, Folder 23
    - Mattson (John R.), Inc., 1933 (Box 46, Folder 965, Reel 38)
    - Mayo, Charles H., 1916-1935 (Box 46, Folder 966, Reel 38)
      See also: Series II, Folder 865
    - Mayo, William J., 1904-1939 (Box 46, Folder 967, Reel 38)
      See also: Folders 34, 1331-1332, Series II, Folders 12, 36, 865
    - Mead, Frederick S.
      See: Series II, Folders 434-435
    - Mead, Katharine R.
      See: Series II, Folder 816
    - Meade (John Paulding) Co., 1931-1932 (Box 46, Folder 968, Reel 38)
    - Meagher, Richard, 1931-1936 (Box 46, Folder 969, Reel 38)
      See also: Series II, Folders 749, 768, 786, 789-790
    - Medical Brotherhood (Fraternitas Medicorum), 1916-1922 (Box 46, Folder 970, Reel 38)
      See also: Folder 1138
    - Medical Library Association, 1926-1931 (Box 46, Folder 971, Reel 38)
    - Medical Society of London, 1923-1928 (Box 46, Folder 972, Reel 38)
      See also: Series II, Folder 660
    - Medical Society of the State of New York, 1920-1937 (Box 46, Folder 973, Reel 38)
    - Mencken, H. L., 1925-1939 (Box 46, Folder 974, Reel 38)
    - Mendel, Lafayette B., 1911-1935 (Box 46, Folder 975, Reel 38)
    - Mendell, Clarence W., 1921-1938 (Box 46, Folder 976, Reel 38)
    - Merchants National Bank: general correspondence, 1922, 1932-1934 (Box 46, Folder 977, Reel 38)
    - Merchants National Bank: general correspondence, 1935-1936 June (Box 47, Folder 978, Reel 38)
    - Merchants National Bank: general correspondence, 1936 July-1939 (Box 47, Folder 979, Reel 38)
    - Merchants National Bank: income tax, 1934-1939 (Box 47, Folder 980, Reel 38)
    - Meredith, J. M., 1937-1939 (Box 47, Folder 981, Reel 38)
    - Merselis, John G.
      See: Series II, Folder 348
    - Messimy, Robert, 1936-1939 (Box 47, Folder 982, Reel 38)